

CHUONG HOANG

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Male



0963.398.222



Oct 30th, 1995

contact@ncsoft.tech

0

St. Tran Dang Ninh, Dist. Cau Giay, Hanoi capital - Vietnam

66

I am a Full-stack Dev with ~8 years of experience in software development both Outsource & Product related to E-commerce, E-payment, Gym management, POS, CRM, etc... Almost all of my mobile/web development knowledge covers planning, designing, coding, testing, and publishing software to Production.

Work experience

Xplor Triib, Full-stack developer

04/2020 - 04/2024

- Participate in building a gym management system for American customers
- Collaborate with the BA/business side to create a technical plan/solution.
- Apply the best practice for the project (Agile, CI/CD, DB-replica, S3 cloud, Mobile auto-deploy, etc...)
- Team management (Vietnam team: 7 members)
- Working on develop/Unit Test/Test Case/Release Web & Mobile (PHP, Angular, Ionic, AWS, EC2)
- Achievement:
- Move all logic from the old app using old technologies to the latest ones.
- Create/Develop/release mobile apps, both iOS & Android, to the Store.
- Develop key features: Stripe, PayPal, Recurring payment, Booking, payment report, etc...
- Recruit and train strong developers for the Vietnam Dev (most of them are middle/senior full-stack devs)
- · Responsibility:
- Rewrite mobile app from Angular S & Ionic 1 to Angular 9 & Ionic 5.
- Develop/maintain both Web (PHP) & Mobile apps (Angular) including features, fixing bugs, writing documents, test cases, unit Tests, and Integration testing for them.
- · Working on Back-end with PHP.
- Create coding/release process for both Web & Mobile.
- Daily meeting with Vietnam & daily report with the Product team.

Setel, Full-stack developer

04/2019 - 04/2020

- Participate in the E-commerce product development process of Malaysian customers.
- Develop both Front-end (Next.js) & Back-end (Nest JS)
- Apply the best practice for the project (Agile, CI/CD, Multi-service)
- Achievement:

Skills

Node.js:

4 years

PHP:

4 years

.NET:

1 year

Angular:

8 years

lonic:

3 years

React:

4 years

React Native:

1 year

Database:

MySQL, MongoDB, SQL Server

Cloud:

ASW, EC2, Docker

Hobbies

Sleep & Travelling

- Create/Develop/Unit Test/Test case/release web app to production (Next.js, React, Nest JS).
- Develop some key features: Order, Payment, Promo, and inventory.
- Responsibility:
- Develop an Admin site using ReactJS.
- Create an E-commerce site using Next.js.
- Working on multiservice APIs with Nest JS.

Connect POS, Full-stack developer

04/2019 - 11/2020

- Participate in the Cloud POS application development process connected with Shopify, BigCommerce, etc...
- Participate create/Develop/Unit Test/Release Front-end web (Angular, React)
- Develop logic for the back-end (PHP)
- Achievement:
- Create an SPA app for shoppers.
- · Responsibility:
- Rewrite the POS web app from AngularJS to Angular 2+
- Develop new features including writing documents, test cases, unit Tests, and Integration testing.
- Create SPA web app ReactJS for consumers.

bePOS, Full-stack developer

11/2018 - 08/2019

- Product link: https://bepos.io/
- Participate in developing sales management applications.
- Work on both Back-end and front-end (Node.js, React, Firebase cloud, Unit Test)
- · Achievement:
- Develop a salary + commission calculation feature for the application.
- · Responsibility:
- Develop POS web app using ReactJS.
- Working with Firebase Cloud API on the back end.

Power Gate, Full-stack developer

04/2016 - 03/2019

- Participate in developing outsourcing projects for European and American customers with many different businesses: E-commerce, Ordering, Delivery, etc...
- Work on both Back-end and front-end (Web & Mobile) (PHP, .NET, Node.js, Angular, React, React Native, Ionic).
- Achievement:
- Build an app yourself from scratch.
- · Responsibility:
- Fresher & Junior with AngularJS/Angular.
- Working with short-term projects as a Front-end developer (Angular/React)
- Working on the back-end API when there are tasks (Node.js, PHP, .NET)

Education

University of transport and communications, Information technology

2013 - 2017

Graduation ranking is pretty good.